(screaming) Call an ambulance!
You know her?
She's one of the girls I killed.
No...
(moaning)
I'm giving you one
more shot. Teddy.
You go to your father's
and look him in the eye.
You fuck this up. and
I'm gonna kill you.
(speaking Spanish)
(door closes)
There's nothing I
wouldn't do for you.
I'm only taking two.
Well. I've got four.
The Volpes already
got enough coke.
and I ain't nickel-and-dimin'
in the Valley.
That's how you get arrested. All
right. all right. all right.
What about. like. Bel Air or some shit?
Unh-unh.
Told y'all I got a cousin
named Devon up in Oakland.
Think I could take the
car for a few hours?
(glass shatters) Aah!
- (grunting)
- Gonna offer you my product.
(speaks Spanish) Get
the fuck out of here.
Órale!
♪♪
♪ Hey. hey! ♪ Come on
♪ Soul
♪ Searching ♪ Hey
(humming)
♪♪
(beads clack) Oh. hello.
Thought you might've
taken off for Vegas.
(chuckles) Well. I was
driving down 52nd.
some kids tossed a baseball.
Smashed your driver's
side window.
You're kidding me.
Mm-hmm. Mmm.
I got it fixed. 50
bucks at Big Earl's.
That's my Cho money.
So I took some more.
"How you doin'. Franklin?"
"Oh. I'm fine. Mama.
Thanks for asking."
Right. right. (chuckles)
Thanks for fixing it. Yeah.
But call me next time. okay?
Didn't wanna interrupt
the spades club.
How'd it go? Hmm.
Me and Agatha was
breakin' fools left and right.
Whoo! Attagirl.
Good for you.
♪ Everywhere I go
(beads clacking)
♪ Soul searching
(singing along) ♪ On the radio
♪ Soul searching everywhere
I go ♪ (buttons clack)
♪♪
Mrs. Hamilton.
Hi. it's. uh. Franklin.
Is Kev up?
Uhh... thank you. (chuckles)
What's up with it?
Talk to me about Oakland.
(man speaking Spanish
on the radio)
(continues in Spanish.
crowd cheering)
(man shouting
excitedly in Spanish)
If we don't start
trusting each other.
these deals are gonna
take a long time.
Are you in a hurry?
(man continues in Spanish)
(door closes)
(beads clack. bag unzips)
Ah! (laughs)
- (exhales deeply)
- órale.
Most of that...
(glass thuds)
goes towards the
next shipment. okay?
So don't get too attached.
Hernan's cut.
(bottle cap clacks)
You're trouble. sabías?
(liquor pours) This is for you.
(glass thuds)
You saved our asses.
Gracias. (glasses clink)
(laughs)
(coughs) Ah!
(speaks Spanish) (sighs)
Are you gonna go give
it to him right now?
Sí. I'll pick up some
food on my way back.
Huh?
Shh.
(breathing heavily)
(thud)
(whispers) Sí.
(breathing heavily)
(door creaks. crickets chirping)
(heavy breathing.
moaning) (door closes)
(unzips)
(heavy breathing continues)
(clattering) GUSTAVO:
(softly) Yeah.
(moaning)
Oh. Oso.
(moaning continues)
Oso.
(panting)
GUSTAVO: Yeah...
(Lucia moans)
It was a mess.
Logan ODing. the girl screaming.
Kristin ran for the
phone. was dialing 9-1-1.
What would you have done?
Let the cops find 50 keys
and a dead CIA officer?
No. see. I would've
told the truth
when the next CIA officer
asked me about it
instead of insisting that
he was paranoid and crazy.
I didn't know you. Couldn't risk
poisoning the well like that.
Yeah. no. I'm here. Go ahead.
(scribbling)
Uh. no. That's...
That's great for now.
Okay.
I'll be in touch. Bye.
They trace the number?
Yeah. the number's registered
to Kristin's apartment.
She mention a roommate
or boyfriend or...
No. but. uh. boyfriend
is unlikely.
TEDDY: Okay. Well.
whoever's looking for her
is staying at her place.
(door closes)
We need to figure
out who that is.
(camera shutter clicks)
(clicks)
(car door opens) (clicks)
(car door closes)
(engine starts)
(clicks)
Jesus.
She looks like her.
Want a beer? Sure.
(telephone ringing) That's the only
intel the agency could get us.
(bottles rattle.
refrigerator door closes)
She's a graduate student?
She was. She dropped out.
(rings)
You want to get that?
(bottle clatters)
She's working as a paralegal.
Hello. I'm not in right now.
Please leave your message after the beep.
Best I can tell...
(machine beeps) after maybe a week
of not hearing from her sister...
JULIA: Hey. it's me. I just wanted to
say hi. she decides to get in the car
and drive out here... look
forward to seeing you...
So we need to figure out
what else she knows.
(scoffs)
She's a grad student.
What can she do?
TEDDY: Exactly what
she's been doing.
She can ask around. she
can make some noise.
She can go to the police.
So I. for one. will sleep
much better knowing
that she's not
gotten any traction.
I imagine probably
you will. too.
And there is. uh. one more thing
I need to talk to you about.
ALEJANDRO: (sighs)
Okay. what's that?
TEDDY: The bodies.
You didn't just dump 'em
in the canyon. did you?
No. I took them all out
of town. buried them.
TEDDY: Where?
ALEJANDRO: Uh. I'm
not sure exactly.
Right. you're not sure exactly
where you buried
three dead girls?
It was somewhere off Highway
14 in the Antelope Valley.
I could take you out
there if you want to.
God. no. I don't... That's...
I just need to know that they're
not gonna be a problem.
ALEJANDRO: Hey. look. I
drove out as far as I could
and I dug until I couldn't
feel my arms. okay?
(lock clicks. door opens)
Now can I ask you a question?
If. by some chance. this... The
sister does have traction...
You mean. if. um.
she's found something that
would jeopardize the op?
Yeah.
Then we have to deter her.
Let's hope it hasn't come to that.
(latches click)
(curtain rings swoosh)
(rustling)
♪♪
(camera shutter clicks)
(camera winds)
(click)
(breathes unevenly)
(horn blares in passing)
(children shouting playfully)
(man shouting in distance)
(laughs) So how far is Oakland?
Oh. man. It's not too bad.
Only. like. seven hours.
- Seven hours?
- Yeah. man.
You know that road
trips take time. man.
It's an experience.
(grunts) Oh...
All right. all right.
Cho got himself a
new butler. huh?
(laughs) You know
where we going?
(door closes)
I thought you've been
to Oakland before.
Once. Way back when. though.
Take a Ding-a-Ling.
Ding Dongs. man.
Hey. you know. Leon ain't
never been outside of L.A.?
Man. whatever. homie. I'm gambling my
life around with you in this bucket.
Hey. don't distract my hoo-ride.
Sure your cousin
got it hooked up?
I told you. my cousin Devon
say he gonna make
sure we straight.
We gonna be straight
when this piece of shit
blow up on the freeway?
(babbles in mocking voice)
Y'all worry too much.
Y'all gonna love Oakland.
So just relax. baby. Damn!
(engine starts)
♪♪
♪ Come on. hit me
We here? Look lively. niggas.
'Bout time. Man. what the fuck?
(motorcycles revving)
I told you he ride.
So we're just gonna
walk two keys
into a damn biker rally?
Man. we can't even
see to get in there.
Should've came strapped.
What part of family do
y'all not understand?
We all good.
I gotta piss. so come on.
(keys jingle)
♪♪
(car doors closing)
Hey. for real. homie.
where the door at?
(grunts)
♪♪
(clattering)
(door squeaks)
♪♪
(door closes. indistinct
conversations)
Hey. the record's
fucking skippin'.
Nicky! Go! (record
needle scratches)
MAN: Fuck that shit. man. Fuck that.
MAN: What's that music?
♪♪
(indistinct conversation)
(bottle shatters) ♪ I'm amazed
♪♪
Hey. who the fuck let y'all in?
Whoa. whoa. hold on. man. Hey...
I'm Devon's cousin.
Little Kev from L.A.?
Devon said if we came up here.
everything would be good and...
- Get out the way. man.
- All right... All right. cool.
(clears throat)
A'ight. so you just gonna
let him know we here then?
Family. huh? That's your
mama's side or your dad's?
Mama's. but I ain't never
really met him like that.
♪♪
MAN: Go ahead. girl! Whoo!
(shouting. laughter)
MAN: Whoo!
♪♪
(bottle shatters)
(conversations continue)
Y'all seen Devon? Oh.
(coughs)
Hey. Kev.
He gonna be here. man.
- The fuck you still so skinny?
- I'm gonna punch you.
- You better punch me.
- (Both laughing)
- What's up. cuz?
- What's up with it?
- Hey. man.
- Yeah. yeah. what...
This place look great. man.
Shit. this the
motherfucking hub here.
- Hey. these my peeps.
- What's up. man?
- What up. homie?
- How's it going?
What up?
You're Two Keys. right?
Franklin. Little Joe here?
No. but you're on the radar.
Kick your feet up for a minute.
The bar over there.
- How long you gonna be?
- Man. we just got here.
Let's do the deal.
get the money.
and get the fuck outta here.
You refusing my
motherfucking hospitality?
Hey. I'm cool to
party while we wait.
They'll like him.
He like to party.
But you refusing my
motherfucking hospitality.
Hey. look. he don't
know no better.
(motorcycle engine
rumbles) Look.
whether Little Joe
rolls up in a minute
or a motherfucking
hour. I can't say.
But he'll be here. A'ight?
All right.
A'ight?
Shit. man. let's have some
fun around this bitch.
Hey. can I get in on that game?
Hell. yeah. I told you.
man. you home. man.
(under breath) Watch that nigga.
We home. man.
Hey. look. so what you gonna do?
You gonna chill? Do your thing. man.
I'm-a hang back.
All right.
♪♪
(sniffs)
You're supposed to be selling.
Come on. man. I just
need a little come up
for the tricks. man.
All right. go find some place.
Last thing I need is these
motherfuckers knowing
I got this shit. all right?
Gettin' into our samples. man.
I'm about to get
in some coochie.
I'll let you know if
she got a friend.
♪♪
(indistinct conversations)
(song ends)
(new dance song begins)
(dice clattering)
(men shouting. laughing)
MAN: Yeah. yeah.
(indistinct conversations)
(buzzing)
I love this song!
Hey. hold still now
before I fuck this up.
(man. woman moaning)
WOMAN: Oh. yeah! (man grunts)
(moaning continues) Y'all
know if Devon in there?
Maybe. Whiteboy Bobby
hotboxing the shit out...
Hey. he brought acid. too.
Hey. hey. hey.
How's she lookin'?
Come on. See for yourself.
- Look at that. man.
- (Man laughs)
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I know. (Chuckles)
I always wanted to be an artist.
But life derailed
my dreams. man.
Hey. you want a tat?
Nah. I'm good. You sure?
Hey. man. I'm good. I did
a dime in San Quentin.
I'm the best. (both laugh)
(motorcycle engine revving)
♪♪
What's up with this
backpack. cutie. huh?
You got class?
Uh... (chuckles) I
got to do somethin'.
♪♪
Yeah. yeah. Ahh...
(laughing)
♪♪
(glass shatters) (man shouts)
(music stops) (crowd shouting)
(woman moaning) MAN: You broke it. man.
You fix it.
Hey. what the fuck
is up in there?
Any word from Little Joe?
Little Joe? MAN: Put the
music back on. man!
Somebody's got blow? Is it him?
He ain't got nothing
that concerns you.
Hey. the fuck he don't.
Why he holding out?
Came here to do a deal. man.
Man. watch your motherfucking
tone when you're around me. man.
WOMAN: Hey! (man shouting)
MAN: Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
(man panting)
Whoa! Her pussy turned into
a fucking mouth on me. man.
(laughing) Her
cooze was a mouth!
WOMAN: It's still just
my pussy. Bobby. Chill.
- (shouting)
- Hey. hey. hey...
Hey. man. where you going?
Put that thing away. man!
WOMAN: Bobby!
(shouting. laughter)
(laughing)
Bobby! Bobby! Yo. that's why I
never licked no pussy right there.
(laughter)
(clattering)
We sold the rest of
the first shipment.
I see that.
The powder wasn't
moving quick enough.
and Alejandro was gonna cut
us off if we couldn't pay.
So you just made a
deal behind my back?
Yeah. with Gustavo's people. He
wanted to keep things simple.
Since when do we care
what Gustavo wants?
Since he found a way
to move the product.
So where's my cut?
Or does he get that. too?
(handle clicks)
(clicks)
(clattering continues)
(exhales sharply)
I made him a partner.
(bag unzips)
It was the only way
he was gonna help us.
(pen clicks) Okay.
Okay? Sure.
You made the deal. you can
pay him out of your end.
Pedro. that's fucked up. More
fucked up than you giving Gustavo
a third of this business
without consulting me? Huh?
I didn't have a choice. You would've done
the same thing. No. I wouldn't have.
What's going on with you?
You're the hardest bitch I know.
and now you're just
giving away our business?
Come on.
Pedro.
(beads clack)
Pedro. we need him.
Bullshit. you like him. I'm
just trying to keep this alive.
You fucking him?
Excuse me?
You heard me.
Tell me you're not. that
it's just business.
Then I'll know I can trust you.
I'm not fucking him.
(sighs)
Bueno.
(exhales deeply)
(door opens. closes)
(bell clangs in distance)
(dog barking in distance)
♪♪
(spits. sniffles)
(Barking continues. siren
wailing in distance)
(coughs)
(sniffles)
(indistinct conversations)
Come on.
(light crackles)
No fucking way.
(siren wailing in distance)
(indistinct conversations)
(Conversations continue.
telephones ringing)
MAN: Sure. that's going to St.
Augustine by this afternoon.
(door closes)
(indistinct conversations)
(conversations continue)
(telephones ringing)
I'm gonna need you to
understand what it is to...
have your dignity.
your self-respect. and make
sure that other people
respect you. too.
Chest out.
Head up.
Shoulders high.
My son.
(telephone rings. echoes)
(conversations fade)
WOMAN: Who are you?
My bad. Sorry. I ain't know
anybody else was in here.
I can go. Hold on.
Are you... okay?
Yeah.
(breathes sharply)
Um...
Do you have any idea
if this used to be
a Black Panther office?
I think it was.
I think I came here when I
was a kid to see my dad.
Well. back when he
was doing his thing.
We're all just doing our thing.
(chuckles softly)
Yeah. I guess.
So what you doin' up in here?
I mean. you too fine to be
hanging out... (exhales)
Come on.
(exhales)
(clinking)
Ta-da. (Chuckles)
Wh-What's that?
It's my new favorite.
Let me see. (giggles)
I-I won't... Ooh. (Giggles)
I-I won't touch it.
Just... hold it out.
(chuckles) Ooh.
Okay. but be careful.
This is the last of it.
(click)
(inhales sharply)
(exhales)
(murmurs)
(exhales sharply)
I ain't never seen that before.
Where you get it from?
You're a star.
You know where to get more?
The star... is a door.
This room...
is a door life.
Is... is life. is all doors.
They're just... you know. they're just...
just opening.
Yeah. Opening...
You on your way to
space. for sure.
(sighs) Opening.
I wanna see what it is.
Go get some more. huh?
(exhales) Oh... I'll buy it.
Oh.
(exhales) I like you. Star.
I like you. too.
(door opens)
(door closes)
(chuckles)
(laughs)
Well. you're not about to
walk around here barefoot?
Why not? It feels...
It feels good.
Well. you're gonna mess
those pretty feet up.
You think they're pretty?
You know you got beautiful feet.
(chuckles) Thank you. Star.
Get that quarter piece. man.
Smoke this right now. brother.
Hey. don't even think about
firing that shit up here.
Move your ass along.
All right. All right. all right.
(train passing)
- What you need. man?
- What's up?
Hey. there. girly girl.
Back already with
them pretty-ass toes?
(laughter)
You got $20?
Uh. $20? Uh. yeah. Mm-hmm.
(chuckling) Uh...$20.
Mm.
(vehicle arrives)
Okay. come on. Let's go.
Uh. actually. I can't right now.
Oh. no... Why don't you go
back to the special place
and maybe I'll see you later?
Huh? (Laughs) Okay.
Bye. Franklin. (laughs)
Mm-hmm. You probably right. yeah.
She fine. but she crazy.
(laughter)
How long's that gonna last her?
I don't know. She'll probably
be back tonight. And it's coke?
Rocked up. yeah.
Why is it so cheap? I
ain't no cook. nigga.
I just move the shit.
I'll buy everything you got.
If you show me who cooked it.
Crossin' a line now. blood.
I ain't got no piece. man.
(humming)
Country motherfucker. What
the fuck are you doing?
No tricks. no games. man.
I just wanna know how y'all
make what y'all making.
(dog barking in distance)
Nice shoes.
You wanna meet the Wizard?
Hell. yeah.
All right. hold down the spot.
Wait. You seriously
gonna take him to Swim?
This nigga got two keys of coke on him.
Hell. yeah.
Let's go. Dorothy.
(sighs)
Oh. watch your shit.
That's mud right there.
(laughs)
- Good looking out.
- Yeah. yeah.
(sighs)
(keys jingling)
(lock clicks. gate creaks open)
Go ahead.
Come on. man.
(hitting key)
Where the fucking E key?
(key playing)
Hey. man. He cool.
He from L.A.
Oh. why you didn't say
that at first. man?
He from L.A.?
So who are you. Michael Jackson?
No. this nigga too dark
to be Michael Jackson.
He more like Sidney Poitier.
No.
I don't know why this
Bobby Womack-ass nigga
brought you here to
my place of business
when he should have had his
ass out there working.
Look. Swim. This nigga
right here cleaned me out
just so he can meet you.
And you see what he packin'.
Nigga. you stupid right now.
It's my fault. I asked.
I just wanna know how y'all
make what y'all makin'.
(Playing notes on
piano. keys tuning)
Go on.
(piano continues tuning)
Go knock that shit off.
and don't come back
till you're done. boy.
(door opens. closes)
What's your name?
Franklin.
They call me Swim. 'cause I'm
either swimming in some money
or swimming in some pussy.
(door opens. closes)
Shit don't make no sense. man.
I agree.
Either you make it
make sense to me.
or I just gotta simplify.
And you know what I mean. right?
I can't tell you if my luck's
been running good or bad. man.
But y'all doing something here
and I'm trying to get in on.
Now. I might be taking
a leap of faith.
Shit. I might be dumb as fuck.
But this shot. this shot.
it feels like it's worth takin'.
'Cause I got things I gotta do.
Things I want.
You understand what I'm sayin'?
If you're the man
cookin' this up.
it means you an artist.
In my experience.
artists create.
and they want the whole
world to experience it.
You an artist. Swim?
Maybe.
So teach me. Show me how
to create the way you do.
I'll take it back to L.A.
and I'll spread the word.
(scoffs)
(mutters indistinctly)
(stairs creak)
♪♪
(glass clinking)
(gate thuds)
Angelico.
We're gonna cook up one
more batch tonight.
SWIM: Keep up now. We
gonna go fast. you dig?
So these Peruvians. right.
when they make they cocaine.
they got this paste.
This cocaine paste at the
bottom of their barrel.
They call it
"bah-say." Nasty shit.
But you take this "bah-say."
you roll it into a cigarette.
that shit gets you
fucked up. Jack.
I had some of my boys who flew
down to Peru for a weekend.
(flames whoosh) They chasing pussy
and whatnot. getting some sunshine.
They smoke this bah-say
with some bitches
and they love it.
Bitches love it. too.
And they keep hearin' it.
Bah-say. bah-say.
bah-say. bah-say.
It keeps going in their head.
Bah-say. bahss. bahss.
bahss. bahss. bahss.
Base.
Come back to the Bay Area
thinkin' that bah-say was
more than what it was.
Pull out their chemistry sets.
try to figure out a way
to free the base
from the cocaine.
They didn't even know what
the fuck they was doing.
but next thing you know. they
unlocked some whole new shit.
And like many other
inventions in America.
it was just a big.
beautiful mistake.
Now crack is the same thing.
but it's cheaper. simpler.
and safer to make.
We don't fuck with no ether
no more. do we. Angel?
Nah. ether do what
ether wanna do.
FRANKLIN: Those the
only ingredients?
It's like bacon and
eggs. Bert and Ernie.
Sometime it only take two things
that complement each other
to make something great.
Peas and carrots.
SWIM: (chuckles) Peas
and fucking carrots.
Now here's the tricky part.
Yeah. You see that?
See those rocks? They're
starting to swim like tadpoles.
(rocks clinking) Can I get high
from breathing these fumes in?
You get a contact. but
you won't get high.
You wanna hit this
shit when we done?
Nah. I don't use.
You should consider
it. my nigga.
That shit open up dark
places in your brain.
these places ain't
never been touched.
Deep. dark places.
Light you up like
you never been lit.
Now here we go. Like the Earth.
she cools down
until she hardens.
(crunching)
Thus creation is born.
You get $50 for this rock. man.
♪ Bee-bop. don't stop
He tweakin'.
FRANKLIN: We can make some more?
SWIM: Shit. How much more?
FRANKLIN: All of it.
♪ Bee-bop. don't... don't...
(indistinct conversations)
WOMAN: And you're
sure about that?
Was anyone there to pick her up?
(telephone ringing)
And is this your first
report about it?
All right.
So what time was that?
Okay.
Hi.
(sighs) Excuse me. Excuse me.
(clears throat) Hi. hi.
Can I just talk to you for just one sec?
(telephone rings)
I just need one sec. It's
about a missing person.
Please. I just need to talk to you.
I'm trying...
I'm trying to find my friend.
She's a missing person.
Her name is Jess Avon.
Please. I know...
I can see that you
are busy here...
Sir. can you please keep
calm and lower your voice?
- We'll get to you when we can.
- Unbelievable.
Excuse me.
(sighs) Sorry. I didn't
mean to bother you.
But did... did you say
that your friend's name
was Jess Avon?
Uh. yeah.
Why? You know her?
No. um. I know of her.
Can we talk for a minute?
Yeah. uh. yeah. yeah. Sure.
Okay.
Oh. I'm Victoria. by the way.
Reed Thompson.
Hi. Um...
(men speaking Spanish)
(truck doors open. close)
(engine starts)
Ay!
Someday soon it's gonna be foot
soldiers doing all the runs
instead of rancheros.
Even though seem to think
nothing's changing.
Too much up for grabs.
These bastards are changing
the tempo of the whole thing
and from prison.
Shit. They're gonna
redraw the whole map.
That's what they're gonna do.
Being boss? Always
looking ahead.
(speaking Spanish)
Yeah? What can you see?
What's up with you?
Nothing.
Listen. the other night
at the party. um.
that's a nice thing you said.
Sorry I got on your
case. you know.
I was. um... you know.
Papa?
I've gotta tell you something.
(click. creaking)
(snoring)
(snorts)
- What time is it?
- (laughs) What's up. man?
Saint.
Little Joe ever show up?
Did he ever. Fuck
is wrong with you?
Devon was mad as hell. man.
You almost got me killed.
Shit would've been
better. though.
I'm never drinking again.
My bad. man. Sorry I left.
Just had to leave. man.
Get my mind right.
- All night?
- Got caught up.
(scoffs)
Come on. man. Open the door.
Shit.
- Shotgun.
- Man. shotgun.
Hey. we hit 7-Eleven
before we hit the highway?
Oh. yeah. Sure. baby. You know.
(unzips bag) Soon as Franklin
tell us why he blew the deal
we drove all the way
the fuck out here for.
And why he got me kicked
out my own cousin's spot.
And where the hell
he been all night.
Then we can go to
7-Eleven. Leon.
(bag rustling)
- What the hell?
- The fuck is that?
Our future.
(scoffs) Man...
Nigga. you crazy. man.
- "Our future."
- LEON: Fool trippin'.
(engine starts) KEVIN:
Fuck you talking about?
LEON: (speaks indistinctly)
KEVIN: I don't wanna hear all that.
We going home.
(zips bag)
- "The future."
- What future?
(engine rumbling)
♪♪
Captions by VITA...